东西都准备好了. 他们正在
北方大酒店等我们.
Everything's set. They're waiting for us
at the Great Northern.
对, 一所木制大房子,
被树木围绕着.
Yeah, a large house made of wood,
surrounded by trees.
在里面的每一个房间
都一模一样,
The house is filled with many rooms
each alike,
却被不同的灵魂所占据
夜复一夜.
but occupied by different souls
night after night.
- 房客都安排到大堂了?
- 都鼎力合作.
- The guests will be in the lobby?
- Full cooperation.
豪克, 你拿到哈罗德·史密斯公寓
的搜查令了?
Hawk, you got that warrant
for Harold Smith's apartment?
我喝完这咖啡
马上就去.
On my way
as soon as l finish my coffee.
豪克, 戈登曾提到
那几页纸--
Hawk, Gordon has mentioned
pages--
我提到过在血毛巾旁
发现了几页纸
What l mentioned were pages
found near the bloody towel
就在犯案地点
火车轨下面
down the train tracks
from the crime site
是从一本日记上撕下来的.
were from a diary.
唐娜·海沃德
说过哈罗德·史密斯
Donna Hayward
spoke of Harold Smith
有劳拉·帕尔默
的一本秘密日记.
having a secret diary
of Laura Palmer's.
可能很重要.
你去查查看.
Could be important.
Let me know what you dig up.
戈登, 我知道你--
Gordon, l understand you're--?
戈登, 我知道你
还要赶去俄勒冈州的本德,是吧?
Gordon, l understand
you're on your way to Bend, Oregon?
我要经过俄勒冈州本德,
公事, 高度机密.
l'm over to Bend, Oregon,
official business, real hush-hush.
祝你们大家好运.
Good luck to all of you.
- 库.
- 戈登.
- Coop.
- Gordon.
好好照顾迈克.
Take good care of Mike.
能认识你们真是太好了.
lt was real nice meeting you fellas.
- 警长.
- 路上小心, 长官.
- Sheriff.
- Safe journey, chief.
谢谢.
Thanks.
不.
No.
警长? 警长!
Sheriff? Sheriff!
警长, 这是什么意思?
到底怎么回事儿?
Sheriff, what's the meaning of this?
What the hell is going on here?
有谁能告诉我
这儿到底在搞什么鬼名堂?
Will somebody please tell me
what the hell is happening here?
到底在这儿搞什么鬼啊?
What in the hell is going on?
史密斯先生.
Mr. Smith.
哈罗德·史密斯?
Harold Smith?
早安.
Morning.
- 早安, 亲爱的.
- 早安, 马蒂.
- Good morning, dear.
- Good morning, Maddy.
利兰姨父.
Uncle Leland.
莎拉姨妈.
Aunt Sarah.
坐. 噢, 好, 喝点咖啡.
好.
Sit. Oh, good, you got some coffee.
Good.
- 昨晚睡得好吗?
- 很好. 谢谢.
- Did you sleep well?
- Very well. Thanks.
我一直在想.
l've been thinking.
我真的很喜欢留在这儿
和这儿的一切.
l've really enjoyed my stay
and everything.
但我觉得该是时候
回家了.
But l really feel like it's time
for me to go home now.
回密苏拉.
To Missoula.
我有自己的工作和公寓.
l've got my job and my apartment.
而且...
And l just...
...该回到我自己的生活了.
...miss having a life of my own.
所以,我想或者明天
就开车回家了.
So l think l'll probably be driving
back home tomorrow.
明天?
Tomorrow?
那好, 我们会非常
挂念你的.
Well, we are going to miss you
very much.
- 但我们完全理解.
- 真的?
- But we also understand completely.
- You do?
- 是的.
- 我们理解. 是, 我们理解.
- We do.
- We do. Yes, we do.
有你在这儿
对我们真是太重要了.
You have been
such a wonderful help.
的确是, 但现在她也该为
自己想想了, 宝贝.
Yes, but now she has to think
about herself, honey.
她有她自己的人生.
She's got her own life.
而且, 你会回来探望我们的,
对吧?
Besides, you'll come back and visit,
won't you?
哦, 这个当然了.
Oh, of course.
我会经常飞奔回来.
l'll come galloping back often.
你把密苏拉讲的好像
在天涯海角似的.
lt's not like Missoula
was at the far end of the universe.
- 不.
- 怎么会.
- No.
- Hardly.
嗯, 那就好.
Well, good then.
没关系.
lt's all right.
记住
我们非常爱你.
Just know that we love you
very much.
我也爱你们.
l love you too.
- 嘿, 那是什么, 一本笔记?
- 对.
- Hey, what's that, a note?
- Yeah.
"我是一个寂寞的灵魂."
''l'm a lonely soul.''
可怜的家伙.
Poor guy.
幸好安迪
没在这儿看到这一幕.
lt's a good thing
Andy didn't see this one.
哦, 是啊.
Oh, yeah.
来看看这个.
Take a look at this.
"这是劳拉·帕尔默的日记."
''This is the diary of Laura Palmer.''
有线索了.
Pay dirt.
看, 我们一共有1,014美元
的帐单要付.
Well, we have bills here
that total $1 ,01 4.
算上保险赔偿金
lncluding the insurance money
只剩下...
that leaves you with...
42美元.
Forty-two dollars.
- 42美元.
- 是个好开始啊.
- Forty-two dollars.
- That's a good start.
42元一个月?
Forty-two dollars for the month?
叫我怎么过啊?
How am l gonna make it?
就靠这42美元
怎么够我们过一个月?
How are we supposed to survive
on $42 a month?
我们? 雪莉, 我不能老骗
我爸妈
We? Shelly, l can't keep telling
my mom and dad
说我每晚都在
麦克家过.
that l'm spending the night
at Mike's.
几点了?
今天的经济课我要迟到了.
What time is it?
l'm missing Economics as it is.
"我们" 是指我和里欧.
''We'' meant me and Leo.
波比, 你说过
你会照顾我们的.
Bobby, you said
you were gonna take care of us.
我会, 雪莉. 我会的.
l am, Shelly. l am.
我想你
把那项链拿回来.
l want you
to take the necklace back.
我们没必要那样做.
We don't have to do that.
我要你把那项链拿回来.
我们需要钱.
l want you to take the necklace back.
We need the money.
雪莉, 你还是先
留着那项链吧.
Shelly, you're gonna
keep this necklace.
我自己都不知道究竟几时
才有足够的资格戴上它?
When am l ever gonna feel
glamorous enough to wear it?
给里欧洗澡的时候戴?
还是给他喂燕麦洲的时候?
Giving Leo a bath?
Feeding him his oatmeal?
那他的卡车呢?
What about his truck?
反正他再也做不成
公路飞车侠了.
He's not gonna be cannonballing
down the highway anytime soon.
- 被警察扣押了.
- 那我们去拿回来啊.
- The police impounded it.
- We can get it back.
他们说那卡车
是运毒工具
They said if it was used
in the commission of a crime
要充公.
it becomes property of the state.
- 但他还没有被起诉啊.
- 规矩又不是我定的.
- He wasn't charged with anything.
- l didn't make the rules.
好了, 好了.
Okay, okay.
你现在怪我吗
好像是我的错了似的.
lt's like you're blaming me
for something.
我没有怪你. 别这样了.
冷静点.
l'm not blaming you. Come on.
Take it easy.
里欧以前和很多人一起
搞过很多东西.
Leo was into a lot of different stuff
with a lot of different people.
应该赚了不少钱的.
He was in it for the money.
波比, 瞧瞧你.
你真的以为里欧有很多钱?
Bobby, look around you.
You really think that Leo had money?
是, 我觉得是.
看看这支票本,
Yes, l do.
Having a look at this checkbook,
我觉得他不可能
存在银行里.
l don't think he ever stepped foot
into a bank.
他肯定把钱藏在
什么地方了.
He must have been hiding it
somewhere.
他醒过来了.
He's alive.
新鞋子.
New shoes.
波比, 他又醒过来了.
Bobby, he's alive.
- 他不是醒, 雪莉.
- 但他说话了.
- He ain't alive, Shelly.
- But he talked.
只是-- 打嗝而已.
他胃里可能有气.
lt's only-- That was a burp.
He probably has gas.
你说那是打嗝?
You call that a burp?
新鞋子.
New shoes.
他最近刚巧买了
新鞋子?
Did he buy any shoes lately
by any chance?
没有.
No.
他只叫我拿一双靴子
去修理.
He had me take in a pair of boots
for repair.
- 几时?
- 上星期.
- When?
- Last week.
- 收据还在吗?
- 在, 干嘛?
- Have you got a receipt?
- Yeah, why?
我不知道.
雪莉, 去吧收据拿来.
l don't know.
Shelly, go get that receipt.
新鞋子.
New shoes.
想要新鞋子吗, 里欧?
Want some new shoes, Leo?
给我们想要的,
我就把整个鞋店买下来给你.
Give us what we want,
l'll buy you the whole damn shoe store.
新鞋子.
New shoes.
爸爸, 关于『单眼杰克』的事
我都知道了.
Daddy, l know about
One-Eyed Jack's.
我不是很明白
你想说什么.
l'm sure l don't know
what you're talking about.
我知道布莱奇,
我知道埃默里·巴提斯,
l know about Blackie,
l know about Emory Battis,
我还知道朗尼特,
和劳拉.
l know about Ronette,
and l know about Laura.
好.
Okay.
我在那里. 看见你了.
l was there. l saw you.
你还记得普鲁登斯?
You remember Prudence?
带着白色小面具的，那就是我.
l wore a little white mask.
我有几个问题需要问你.
l need to ask you some questions.
问吧.
Ask away.
你开『单眼杰克』
多久了?
How long have you owned
One-Eyed Jack's?
5年了.
Five years.
你知道劳拉在那里工作吗?
Did you know Laura worked there?
她只在那儿呆过一阵子.
She was only there for a brief time.
- 我是问你知不知道?
- 知道.
- Did you know?
- Yes.
你有怂恿过她
去那里工作吗?
Did you in any way encourage her
to work there?
没有. 我都不知道.
No. l had no idea.
她自己要求说想在
百货店商场工作.
She asked if she could work
in the department store.
巴提斯没问过我就把她去送去那里了.
Battis sent her without my knowing.
你和她睡过了?
Did you sleep with her?
是吗?
Did you?
是.
Yes.
是你杀了她吗?
Did you kill her?
我爱她.
l loved her.
诺玛, 能和你
讲几句吗?
Norma, can l talk to you
for a second?
当然. 怎么了?
Sure. What's up?
自从里欧回家后，所有事都...
With Leo coming home and all...
...我应该留在家里
看护他的.
...l'm supposed to be there
to watch him.
而且估计
要全天候了.
And it looks like
it's gonna be a full-time thing.
所以我在想
So l was thinking
必须把工作辞了.
that l have to quit my job.
总之先过一段时间吧.
Just for a little while anyway.
我好难过.
l'm sorry.
之前我自己还保证过
不会这样做的.
l promised myself
l wasn't gonna do this.
不要紧的, 甜心.
lt's all right, sweetheart.
我感觉糟透了.
l just feel so bad.
我爱你, 也爱在这儿工作.
l love you. l love working here.
我实在不想令你失望.
l don't wanna let you down.
你不会让我失望的.
You're not gonna let me down.
不会吗?
l'm not?
瞧, 雪莉, 你有自己的生活
也有自己的事要操心.
Look, Shelly, you've got your own life
to worry about.
我这儿没问题的.
l'll be fine here.
- 真的吗?
- 真的.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
现在, 你要照顾好自己.
Now, you look after yourself.
登你安顿好,
就可以回来了.
When you're ready,
you can come right back.
一切如常
就像你从没离开过.
lt'll be like you haven't even
missed a day.
你会让我重新回来?
You'll let me come back?
你要是到别的地方工作
试试看,我可不饶你.
You just try to take a job someplace
else and see what happens.
我都不知该说什么好了.
l don't know what to say.
什么都别说了.
Don't say anything.
我告诉他了
我原来打算和爸妈去旅行,
And l told him l'd been traveling
with my parents,
但我现在想先报读
春季班.
but now l wanted to register
for spring semester.
哦, 小艾艾, 我们坐柜台这边吧.
Oh, Eddie, let's sit at the counter.
我太想喝巧克力奶昔了,
你想喝不?
l'm just dying for a chocolate shake,
aren't you?
嗨, 诺玛.
Hi, Norma.
快说, 你在这工作
多久了?
Say, how long have you
been working here?
嗯, 到4月就满20年了.
Well, it's 20 years this April.
噢, 你别开玩笑了.
Oh, you kidder.
她太搞笑了.
What a kidder.
嗯, 才6周而已,
对不对, 诺玛?
Well, it's been about six weeks,
isn't that right, Norma?
大约6周.
About six weeks.
- 噢, 啊, 对.
- 嗯, 你知道吗?
- Oh, yeah, that's right.
- Well, you see?
当你给爸妈硬是拉去欧洲
或别处玩一个月,
When your parents drag you off
to Europe or someplace for a month,
之后, 你再回来,
就会像离开很久似的.
then, when you get back,
it's like you've been away forever.
2杯巧克力奶昔,
谢谢, 诺玛.
Two chocolate shakes,
please, Norma.
- 我要咖啡.
- 我要加生奶油.
- Coffee for me.
- Extra whipped cream on mine.
你好.
Hi.
- 你叫什么?
- 雪莉.
- What's your name?
- Shelly.
你在学校和我同班么?
Are you in our class at school?
我想不是.
l don't think so.
我去拿奶昔和咖啡.
l'll get the shake and coffee.
- 欧洲?
- 是啊.
- Europe?
- Yeah.
我爸妈爱上那里了
现在还呆在那儿呢.
My parents loved it so much
they're still there.
难以置信吧?
Can you believe it?
他们还说我可以
呆在小艾艾家呢.
And they said it was okay
for me to stay over at Eddie's.
那房子到底是我父母的
还是我的, 小艾艾?
ls it your parents' house
or mine, Eddie?
就是.
That's right.
哦, 说, 诺玛,
你会不会生气或别的
Oh, say, Norma,
you're not mad or anything
因为小艾艾正和我约会,
你会不高兴吗?
because Eddie's sort of taking me out,
are you?
你和艾德? 不. 不.
我怎么会呢?
You and Ed? No. No.
Why should l be?
噢, 没别的.
因为小艾艾告诉我你刚分手了.
Oh, no reason.
Eddie told me you broke up.
我就是...
lt's just that...
...就是太为他陶醉了.
...l'm just so sweet on him.
- 他实在太迷人了,不是吗?
- 纳丁.
- lsn't he just the dreamiest?
- Nadine.
真等不及
足球季快点到就好了.
l can't wait
for the start of football season.
- 你觉得呢?
- 不. 我也等不及了.
- Can you?
- No. Can't wait.
我也是.
Me neither.
我真的好开心.
l am just so happy.
- 噢, 纳丁.
- 噢, 天啊, 对不起.
- Oh, Nadine.
- Oh, God, l'm sorry.
- 你是怎么做到的?
- 又给我压爆了一个.
- How'd you do that?
- There goes another one.
这个玻璃杯之前
肯定有裂痕.
There must've been a crack
in this glass from before.
- 天啊.
- 那不算.
- Golly.
- Don't count on it.
我最近老笨手笨脚的.
l'm so clumsy lately.
连我自己都不敢相信.
l can hardly believe it.
雪莉, 去拿止血贴,
我去拿毛巾.
Shelly, get those Band-Aids,
and l'll get a towel.
噢, 小艾艾.
Oh, Eddie.
我太开心了
l am so happy
我能亲吻你至死为止.
l could just kiss you to death.
噢, 你小子, 纳丁.
Oh, boy, Nadine.
我想她还在店里. 雪莉.
l think she's at the diner. Shelly.
雪莉.
Shelly.
他在那, 麦克.
全新里欧·强生.
There he is, Mike.
The late Leo Johnson.
- 是汉克干的?
- 不是他是谁.
- Hank did this?
- He sure as hell did.
他就站在那扇窗户
开枪射进来.
He shot him through that window
right there.
里欧, 我去鞋店了.
Leo, l went to the shoe shop.
我给他们看收据,
然后你看他们给我什么了.
l showed them the ticket,
and look what they gave me.
- 新鞋子.
- 才不是, 你这傻帽, 是旧鞋.
- New shoes.
- No, you knucklehead, old shoes.
里欧, 他念念不忘鞋子这事儿.
Leo, he gets pretty fixated.
我到希望他永远惦记这事儿.
l hope he gets permanently fixated.
我太他妈的了解你了, 里欧.
l know you too damn well, Leo.
鞋子里肯定有鬼名堂,
没错吧?
Something about these shoes,
isn't there?
肯定有些事
跟这些鞋子有关.
There's something
with these shoes.
我听说过有人, 你知道吗,
在他们的靴子里塞东西.
l heard about people, you know,
muling stuff in their boot.
啥, 你以为
我没检查过吗?
What, do you think
l didn't check these out?
你有锤子吗?
Would you get a hammer?
别乱跑, 里欧.
Don't go anywhere, Leo.
噢, 我的天啊.
Oh, my God.
- 那是什么, 一盘磁带?
- 别碰.
- What is that, a tape?
- Don't.
别再吐口水了, 伙计.
Quit spitting, man.
咳, 又不是钱.
Well, it's not money.
但谁知道呢?
But who knows?
黛安, 下午2:47.
Diane, it's 2:4 7 p.m.
我现在警局的
会议室里
l'm in the conference room
at the sheriff's station
在看劳拉·帕尔默
残存的秘密日记.
with the remains
of Laura Palmer's secret diary.
很棘手
它已经残缺不全了.
A great deal of it
has been mutilated.
很多我之前已经
推测过的论点
Much of what l've been able
to decipher
都得到了
独臂人的论证.
supports the contention
of the one-armed man.
它们一再显示了
鲍勃的存在.
There are repeated references
to a Bob.
从她青春期开始
他就一直存在并威胁着她.
He was a threatening presence
in her life from early adolescence.
这里的信息还显示
虐待和性骚扰是家常便饭.
There are intimations of abuse
and molestation on a regular basis.
他还提到,
在多个场合中,
He is referred to,
on more than one occasion,
以她父亲朋友的身份出现.
as a friend of her father's.
而我刚刚才发现
And l just uncovered this entry
她死前
2周写道:
dated less than two weeks
before her death:
"终有一天我会把
本·荷恩公诸于众.
''Someday l'm gonna tell the world
about Ben Horne.
我要让大家知道
本·荷恩到底是个什么样的人."
l'm gonna tell them
who Ben Horne really is.''
请进?
Yes?
- 欧蕊.
- 我必须要见你.
- Audrey.
- l had to see you.
- 很抱歉打断你工作.
- 你现在感觉怎样?
- l'm sorry if l'm interrupting you.
- How are you feeling?
- 我和父亲谈过了.
- 如何?
- l spoke with my father.
- Yeah?
他和她睡过了.
He was sleeping with her.
和劳拉.
With Laura.
我也不知道他们有多久,
可能有好一阵子了.
l don't know for how long,
maybe quite a while.
我的神啊.
Holy smokes.
她当时在『单眼杰克』,
那儿工作.
She was up at One-Eyed Jack's,
working there.
我发现,
原来那里是属于他的.
And he owns the place,
that's what l found out.
- 他亲口告诉你的?
- 对.
- He told you this?
- Yes.
你打算怎么做?
What are you gonna do?
哈里.
Harry.
你打算怎么做?
你要逮捕他吗?
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna arrest him?
好, 我不想你和任何人
说这件事，一个字也别提.
Audrey, l don't want you to say
a word about this to anyone.
- 好的.
- 很好. 现在, 先回家.
- Okay.
- Okay. Now, go on home.
怎么了?
What's going on?
别用药，他会指引你.
Without chemicals he points.
今早在北方大酒店,
当那个人走进房间时
This morning at the Great Northern,
Mike reached for his arm and fainted
迈克伸手去摸断臂那边
而且还忽然变得很虚弱.
just when a certain person
walked into the room.
哈里, 我们需要一份搜查令了.
Harry, we need a warrant.
一份拘捕本杰明·荷恩
的搜查令.
A warrant for the arrest
of Benjamin Horne.
好消息, 托吉麻辣先生.
Good news, Mr. Tojamura.
我弟弟, 杰利,
和你在大阪的人谈过了,
My brother, Jerry,
spoke to your people in Osaka,
也核对过你提供
的东京银行的资料,
checked your references
at the Tokyo bank,
对于你向我们提出的计划,
我的好朋友,
and the answer to your proposal,
my good friend,
一致通过了.
is a big thumbs up.
我们也感谢你的迅速行动.
We appreciate your promptness.
我们太高兴了
简直无法用言语来形容,
Speaking for the entire community
of Twin Peaks,
我谨代表双峰镇全体居民
l cannot tell you how pleased we are
热烈欢迎你
加入格斯伍计划.
to welcome you
into the Ghostwood fold.
非常感谢你.
Thank you so much.
- 合同. 请你过目.
- 我会尽快审批,和--
- Contract. For your perusal.
- And a fast approval l--
警局.
Sheriff.
- 这是干什么?
- 警察办案.
- What is this?
- This is police business.
请你跟我们走一趟.
We'd like you to come with us.
好. 但我正巧在开会.
Fine. l happen to be in a meeting.
你能给我个合理的解释吗?
Could you be a little more specific?
你现在是劳拉·帕尔默谋杀案
的头号嫌疑人了.
You're wanted for questioning
in the murder of Laura Palmer.
这个解释够合理了吧?
ls that specific enough for you?
你神经病. 简直是神经.
You're insane. lnsane.
托吉麻辣先生, 我肯定这是个
极其严重的误会.
Mr. Tojamura, l'm sure that this
is some dreadful mistake.
你是乖乖合作呢
You can come quietly
还是要我们用手铐拉着你
穿过酒店大堂呢.
or we can drag you through your lobby
in handcuffs.
库珀, 你们在恶意
玩弄我吗?
Cooper, is this some sort
of sick joke?
如果是,
我警告你,我可认识很多高官.
Because if it is,
l know people in high places.
你最好照他说的办.
You'd better do what he says.
滚.
Go away.
滚出这里. 滚开, 快滚.
Get out of here. Go on, go on.
我要去吃三文治了.
l'm gonna go out for a sandwich.
不! 不! 不!
No! No! No!
不! 不!
No! No!
你们--
You--
不! 你们不能这样对我.
No! You can't do this to me.
- 既成事实了.
- 你们--
- lt's already done.
- You--
利兰.
Leland.
先把他关到拘留室.
Take him down to the holding cell.
我们不知道将会发生什么
或什么时候发生,
We don't know what will happen
or when,
但猫头鹰们
会会出现在公路小屋.
but there are owls
in the Roadhouse.
公路小屋.
The Roadhouse.
有事要发生了,
是吗, 玛格利特?
Something is happening,
isn't it, Margaret?
是的.
Yes.
喂, 看着我, 老兄,
你给我小心点.
Say, look here, buster,
you just watch it.
自从我们相遇,
我就被你莫名其妙的吸引了.
Since the moment we met,
l have been strangely attracted to you.
你最好马上给我滚出这里,
先生.
You just better get the hell out of here,
mister.
看看你的双眼,
那么温暖...
There's something about your eyes,
so warm...
...和深沉.
...and deep.
蓝如天际
And blue as the sky.
蠢货, 是我. 是我啊.
Dummy, it's me. lt's me.
凯萨琳?
Catherine?
你样子好可怕.
You look terrible.
太可怕了.
Just terrible.
真 太可怕了.
告诉你的心我是唯一
Tell your heart that l'm the one
告诉你的心那就是我
Tell your heart it's me
- 你知道哈罗德·史密斯的事了吗?
- 知道.
- You heard about Harold Smith?
- Yeah.
不是任何人的错.
lt's not anybody's fault.
他有病.
He was a sick man.
我想他的内心一定在某种程度上很受伤
而我却没能帮助他.
l think he was hurt inside
in a way l couldn't figure out.
每个人内心都受过伤.
Everybody's hurt inside.
他的一生都在那个房子里,
我却亵渎了它,毁了它.
His whole life was in that house,
and l violated that.
你只是想找到
有关劳拉的事.
You were just trying to find out
about Laura.
詹姆斯, 他死了.
James, he's dead.
他不该遭那个罪.
He didn't deserve that.
影子在我屋里
Shadow in my house
那个人, 他有棕色的双眼
The man, he has brown eyes
杜鲁门警长.
Sheriff Truman.
爱让我感动
Love moves me
我要你
在我心里来回摇荡
l want you
Rockin' back inside my heart
我要你
在我心里来回摇荡
l want you
Rockin' back inside my heart
马蒂要走了.
Maddy's leaving.
是吗?
She is?
是, 她准备回家了.
Yeah, she's gonna go home.
那就怪了.
她从来没向我提起过.
That's weird.
She never said anything to me.
告诉你的心你让我哭泣了
Tell your heart you make me cry
告诉你的心不会让我死去
Tell your heart don't let me die
我要你
在我心里来回摇荡
l want you
Rockin' back inside my heart
我要你
在我心里来回摇荡
l want you
Rockin' back inside my heart
在我心里来回摇荡
影子在我屋里
Shadow in my house
尘埃到处飞舞
Dust is dancing in the space
狗和鸟儿彼此远离
A dog and bird are far away
日初日落
日日如是
The sun comes up and down
Each day
它又发生了.
lt is happening again.
莎拉姨妈?
Aunt Sarah?
利兰姨父?
Uncle Leland?
莎拉姨妈, 利兰姨父,
那是什么味道?
Aunt Sarah, Uncle Leland,
what is that smell?
好像有东西烧着了.
lt smells like something's burning.
啊, 我的天啊. 莎拉姨妈?
Oh, my gosh. Aunt Sarah?
来人啊, 救命!
Somebody, help me!
救救我!
Help me!
劳拉. 劳拉.
Laura. Laura.
劳拉. 劳拉. 劳拉.
Laura. Laura. Laura.
劳拉, 我的宝贝儿.
Laura, my baby.
劳拉. 劳拉.
Laura. Laura.
劳拉.
Laura.
利兰说...
Leland says...
...你打算回密苏拉,
蒙大拿州!
...you're going back to Missoula,
Montana!
尘埃到处飞舞
Dust is dancing in the space
我深感遗憾.
l'm so sorry.
日初日落
日日如是
The sun comes up and down
Each day
川流奔向大海
The river flows out to the sea
爱, 请别离开
Love, don't go away
回到这儿来
Come back this way
回来,留下吧
Come back and stay
永恒不息
Forever and ever